{
  "Addition (plus 5s)": [
    {
      "question": "0 + 5",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 5",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 5",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 5",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 5",
      "choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 5",
      "choices": ["7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 5",
      "choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 5",
      "choices": ["7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 5",
      "choices": ["9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 5",
      "choices": ["10", "11", "12", "13", "14", 15, 16, 17, 18],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 0",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 1",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 2",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 3",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 4",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 5",
      "choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", 14, 15],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 6",
      "choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", 14, 15],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 7",
      "choices": ["7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", 14, 15],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 8",
      "choices": ["8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", 14, 15],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 9",
      "choices": ["10", "11", "12", "13", "14", 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "14"
    }
  ],
  "Addition (plus 4s)": [
    {
      "question": "0 + 4",
      "choices": ["3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 4",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 4",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 4",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 4",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 4",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 4",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 4",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 4",
      "choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 4",
      "choices": ["7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 0",
      "choices": ["3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 1",
      "choices": ["3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 2",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 3",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 4",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 5",
      "choices": ["3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 6",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 7",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 8",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 9",
      "choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "13"
    }
  ],
  "Addition (plus 3s)": [
    {
      "question": "0 + 3",
      "choices": ["3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 3",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 3",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 3",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 3",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 3",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 3",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 3",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 3",
      "choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 3",
      "choices": ["7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 0",
      "choices": ["3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 1",
      "choices": ["3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 2",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 3",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 4",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 5",
      "choices": ["3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 6",
      "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 7",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 8",
      "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 9",
      "choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "12"
    }
  ],
  "Addition (plus 2s)": [
    {
      "question": "0 + 2",
      "choices": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 2",
      "choices": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 2",
      "choices": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 2",
      "choices": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 2",
      "choices": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 2",
      "choices": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 2",
      "choices": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 2",
      "choices": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 2",
      "choices": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 2",
      "choices": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12"],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": "12"
    }
  ]
}
